Mishty.
Come on, hurry up.
We don't want to miss the train.
Or you'll end up
spending your summer break at home.
My little swallow!
You look so pretty.
Tiny little swallow
Cute little swallow
Gone?
Flying, flying far away
She lost her way and went astray
Ah…
Green mango!
Papa, green mangoes.
You want green mangoes, my love?
I'll go right away.
Don't take too long. Come back soon.
Yeah, I'll be back soon. Just two minutes.
It's time for green mangoes.
-Mamma.
-Hmm?
Let's go.
Train-train?
Chuck-chuck goes the train and…
Let me open it.
There you go.
Stay right here.
Don't go anywhere. Okay?
And while I'm in the bathroom,
we'll sing the swallow song together, hmm?
But first, you'll sing.
Okay, my little swallow.
Come on, let's start.
Tiny little swallow
Cute little swallow
Lost in the woods
This little swallow
Flying, flying far away
She lost her way and went astray
On a branch, all alone
No friend to call her own
Then another came, laughing by
Ho, ho, swallow
Burst herself up there so high
Hello, swallow Hello, swallow
Little friends, where did they fly?
…ready for departure…
Mishty?
…and take care of your belongings.
Mishty. Mi--
Mishty!
-Mishty! Mishty!
-Where are you going?
-Mamma!
-Stop that woman! She's taking my child.
Wait!
Mishty!
Watch out! Where are you going?
Mishty! Mishty! Mishty!
Get away! Help, please!
-Help me!
-Mishty! Someone stop her!
Mamma!
Mishty!
Mishty.
Mamma.
Mishty!
Bani!
What happened?
Say something, Bani!
Bani!
Can you hear me, Bani?
Where's Mishty?
Bani!
Slow down, Bani, slow down. Wait.
-This way.
-Yeah.
Sir, someone's kidnapped my daughter, sir.
This way.
-Sit here, Bani. I'll tell him.
-Careful, careful.
A woman kidnapped my daughter
from the train station.
Please do something, sir.
-Can you describe her?
-Bani.
Yeah, yeah. Pur-pur-pur-purple--
She was wearing a purple saree.
Her head was covered. I…
-I couldn't see her face.
-Did you get into a fight?
No, sir. We don't even live here.
We were going to Gomati for a holiday.
I got off for two minutes
to buy green mangoes for my daughter,
and that's when all this happened.
I was too far away
to be able to catch the woman.
-Okay. Details, quickly, officer.
-Please, sir.
Tell him everything.
-But before that, get them first aid.
-But, sir…
-Okay. Later.
-Sir, please try and understand.
-Listen to me, sir, it's been two hours…
-We'll look into it.
-Don't worry.
-They'll do something to her.
Sir, I beg of you.
-Sir, please. Sir!
-Gokul?
Where did the officer go?
Can you see anything?
No.
Nurse, get the dressing done, please.
Come. This way.
It's a trauma-related injury.
And an internal hemorrhage has caused
temporary blindness in both eyes.
She'll be fine
with some rest and medication.
But not sure how long
before she can see again.
Gokul.
Gokul, please ask him again.
It's been six hours, Gokul.
Please ask them where is my daughter.
We're just waiting around, Gokul.
Please go.
Why don't you ask them again?
Are you listening?
Sir, listen to me.
It's been six hours
since we filed a report for my daughter.
-Is there any update?
-Oh, yes.
Uh, look, your daughter's pictures
have been sent
to all the nearby police stations.
Uh, we should be getting an update
in a few hours.
-Can you please help me?
-Gokul!
Take me there
and let me ask them if you can't.
It's been… It's been a while.
Why aren't they telling us anything?
Please go and sit down.
I'm writing a report.
Please understand the urgency
of the situation.
Please go and sit.
You sitting on my head
won't solve anything, hmm?
Go and tell the officer that
the woman was running
on platform number six.
Bani.
-She's been hurt badly on her head.
-Really, sir?
A while back, we asked her what happened--
Apparently, if a child isn't found
in 48 hours, then, uh,
most likely, they're never found.
Really feeling sorry for them.
No.
No, no.
Tiny little swallow Cute little swallow
Flying, flying far away
She lost her way and went astray
JOYPURRA POLICE
-Hey?
-Ah.
-You're still sitting here?
-Sir.
It's really late. Please go home.
-You two please leave!
-Tell me what's happening, sir.
Sir?
My daughter, where is she, sir?
Please eat this, sir.
Um…
Please eat something.
Thank you.
Here, Bani. Eat something.
No.
You're a blessing from the Lord
My darling
For a smile of yours
I can sacrifice
The whole world
Hey! What the h--
The officer is coming this way.
I'll talk to him.
Okay.
Pandey, hurry up. Give me a cup of tea.
-Sir…
-Come on, hurry up, please.
Wait, wait, just a moment.
-There's no news of my daughter.
-Cream roll.
-Can you talk to the senior officer?
-Forget about the senior officer.
His boss has arrived
at the station. Kabir.
-Now go sit down.
-Please let me talk to the senior officer.
All right, all right. I'll speak to him.
Attention, everyone, please.
Kabir sir will conduct a special briefing.
Sir…
No, thank you.
I don't drink tea.
This is the third case of abduction
in Joypurra this month.
First, a six-year-old girl gets abducted
from a bus station.
-Where is Shalini? Where did she go?
-Huh?
-Tell me.
-My girl.
-Where's our daughter? Our child!
-Our daughter!
That too in broad daylight in public view.
Then from the outskirts,
another six-year-old abducted.
-Where are you? I've been waiting for you.
-Mamma! Boo-hoo.
Tell me, have you taken the sweets?
Asmita!
And yesterday,
from the train station,
another five-year-old girl abducted.
I want to know
what have you been able to find out
about these kidnappings?
Um…
Sir, we're doing our best.
I mean, friends, family, enemies,
we're questioning everyone.
But honestly, sir,
I find it very difficult to understand
why would such senior officers like you
be sent here for a few kidnappings.
This case is beyond
just a few kidnappings, Mr. Saha.
For you, it might just be
three separate kidnappings,
but all of these are interlinked.
And that is why I was sent here.
This is part
of a massive sex trafficking racket.
In 2023, India had more than
80,000 cases of abduction.
And a major part of it
was of the sex trafficking of minors.
Now most of these kids
where taken from the East Coast
and its surrounding areas.
We know that there are two things common
to these kidnappings.
First, that all the girls
that were kidnapped
are younger than six years of age.
And second, they're the daughters
of helpless low-class parents.
There is an increased demand
for these girls in the flesh trade.
So it is very important for us to find out
how they're doing it.
What's the modus operandi?
How and from where are they being smuggled
out of the country?
Now the border towns of the East Coast
and its surrounding areas
are going to be the focus
of our investigation.
To begin with, we need network.
Only then, can we investigate.
Hmm.
Mr. Kallol.
IT departments of all other cities
have submitted
their updated surveillance reports.
But Joypurra's department hasn't.
May I know why?
Sir.
They must have a pretty strong network.
Not like ours.
Uh, it's in process though.
Sir.
We have ensured to cover
each and every route
leading out of Joypurra. Yeah?
Good.
Barricade these areas.
And I want every exit from Joypurra
to be sealed immediately.
Got it?
After you, sir.
Thank you.
You may get back to your work.
Joypurra is not
everyone's cup of tea, sir.
Remember that.
Uh, how much?
You can pay me later
once you find your daughter.
Thank you.
Sir, my daughter is missing.
-Give me few, please.
-Come. Hey.
-Careful. I'm going in.
-Yes.
-Sir.
-That's my daughter.
If any of you see her,
please call this number.
-Stay right here.
-Okay.
-My daughter's kidnapped.
-Please wait.
Please, please help me find my daughter.
This is my daughter. Have you seen her?
If you find her, call this number, please.
My daughter was kidnapped
from the railway station yesterday.
We've been looking for her.
And the police aren't doing much.
If you get to know anything,
please can you call me on this number?
There is an NGO and shelter home
for children nearby.
Shishukal.
Perhaps, they might be able to help.
-Sorry. Sorry.
-Bani!
Sorry.
I dropped them. I dropped them.
I dropped them.
-I dropped them. I dropped them.
-Bani!
-Gokul, I dropped them, Gokul.
They took her away.
Runaway, abducted, or missing.
This place has information
on all these children.
Please leave
your daughter's picture with us.
I'll get the form for you both.
We need to know everything about her.
Please fill it correctly, all right?
Don't worry.
City of Joypurra's blessed
by the Goddess Chaumukhi.
Your daughter will return to you safely.
Sir.
The train station and toll checkpoint,
both had just one gate operational.
The rest have been shut down.
In keeping with
our threat assessment reports,
we have increased security everywhere.
Twenty-four-seven
camera surveillance is on.
Special forces are present
on every route leading out of the city.
Now it's impossible
for the girls to be taken out of Joypurra.
What about the underground
drug smuggling routes?
Let me explain. Look.
With the help of drones and GPR,
your JSF have conducted
an anti-tunnelling operation.
As you can see in the video,
all the tunnels are shut.
And all the tunnels that are shut
have been sealed off officially.
Madam is absolutely right.
Mark my words.
Uh, forget about the girls,
even an ant can't leave Joypurra.
Is this confirmed?
-Sir, uh…
-I repeat.
Even an ant can't leave Joypurra.
Train halted at the platform.
Gokul had gone to get green mango.
Mishty wanted to go to the bathroom.
Then I went in.
I asked her to stand right there
for just two minutes.
She was standing right outside.
-I told her she was… She was…
-Bani.
Have some tea, Bani.
She was singing the Swallow song…
-Bani.
-She was singing the Swallow song with me.
And we were doing it--
It's been two days
you haven't eaten anything.
At least have some tea, Bani.
She was reciting it for me…
I should have taken her inside.
I shouldn't have…
I shouldn't have left her outside.
-I shouldn't have--
-Bani.
-I don't know how I could be so careless.
-Bani!
It's my fault. I shouldn't…
Get a grip. We'll find her.
Tell me how, Gokul?
It's been more than 24 hours,
and we're just sitting here.
What have you been able to do? Huh?
-And this thing is so frustrating.
-Bani!
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
How we're going to find Mishty?
We can't just be sitting around here.
You think those officers
are going to find her?
Those guys, they don't even talk to us.
I just want my daughter back.
Bring me my Mishty, Gokul.
-Bring me my Mishty!
-What do you mean, "My Mishty"?
She is my daughter too. I'll find her!
Go and find her then!
Get my daughter back in here! Huh?
We couldn't protect her, Gokul.
You couldn't protect your daughter.
What condition she might be in,
what kind of people she might be with!
She… She must be waiting hoping
that her parents will come find her.
And look at her parents
just sitting around.
Just bring my daughter back.
Whatever it takes.
I don't care.
Just bring me my daughter.
Bring her back now.
Bring my Mishty back.
My Mishty…
Please bring my Mishty back to me.
I want my Mishty.
I want my Mishty, Gokul.
I'm going back to train station now.
Hopefully, this time,
I'll be able to find out something more.
You wait here for me. I'll be back.
You wanted to see me?
Yeah.
Sanjukta.
We've been tipped off
by the local intelligence.
And, uh, as per our sources…
Uh, good evening, sir.
Come.
As per our sources,
this is the gang we've dealt with before.
The Blackhole.
And that's the same gang
which was smuggling girls
out of the country
from the Fanapur border five years ago.
Exactly.
At that time, we were onto them.
Through phone calls,
bank transfers, social media.
But the moment they realized
we're after them,
they shut down the operation
and vanished completely.
We couldn't--
But this time,
they're playing it differently.
They are not leaving
any digital footprint.
And according to our intel,
a huge consignment of these poor girls
will leave the country
in a month and half.
From a border town.
-Spicy puffed rice!
-So, there's a great chance
that until then
these girls will be kept hidden,
-possibly in nearby areas.
-Spicy puffed rice!
We just need to figure out
which border town is it going to be.
Spicy puffed rice!
Dutta Sir!
Take it or the monkeys will steal it.
Sir, spicy puffed rice.
Spicy puffed rice!
Be very careful, Sanjukta.
Every corner of this place
is infested with snakes.
And the criminals
could even be in uniform.
Dada Bhai, the new officer is a tough one.
He has increased the security everywhere.
Do you think we should delay
the consignment of girls a little?
The girls will leave
in a month and a half.
Make sure you're ready with Plan Zero.
A cup of tea.
Liliya.
Liliya, my dear.
You were only six when I began
teaching you acrobatic tricks.
But I never taught you to give up.
Jhunu Amba?
A defeated mother cannot be my daughter.
That's not my Liliya.
Jhunu Amba.
They took away my daughter
from me, Jhunu Amba.
They took her away.
They took her away
right in front of my eyes,
and I stood there helpless.
Why my Mishty?
My daughter, my little swallow.
They took her away.
Life is a chain of events.
The past, the present and the future
are all connected.
Seven years ago,
when you left Chaksuliyapada
and went to the city
to perform acrobatics,
my granddaughter, Dulari,
was kidnapped by some people.
For years I looked for her,
but I couldn't find her.
Just two years ago,
I got to know about a gang…
A gang by the name of Blackhole.
She was kidnapped by them.
With great difficulty,
after connecting the dots,
I've arrived here.
G… Gang?
My… My Mishty.
My Mishty was kidnapped by…
-Pull yourself together, Liliya.
-They took my Mishty.
It's believed that centuries ago,
there lived a demon here
by the name of Magrasur.
He kidnapped children
and took them to the netherworld.
To save them,
Chaumukhi the goddess of this land herself
descended into the netherworld.
She tore open Magrasur's belly
and freed those children.
-How…
-Keep the faith.
-How would she…
-Be strong.
What condition must she be in?
Liliya.
-Has she eaten anything at all?
-Liliya.
Listen to me very carefully.
We are going to find your daughter Mishty.
I had overheard an officer
at the police station.
He mentioned that this gang
keeps girls hidden
in Joypurra and its neighboring areas.
They plan to smuggle them out of here
in about four to six weeks.
Mishty could be one of those girls.
You need to stay here
and fight these demons.
One… One thing I'm sure of, Jhunu Amba.
Until I get my daughter back,
I will not leave Joypurra.
For that,
you'll have to first hide your fears,
and get to know this city well.
To save your Mishty,
you will have to become
a part of this city.
Just like I have become.
Hello, Bani ma'am.
Please settle your laundry bills.
I need to see my money quickly.
Tomorrow. Don't bother me right now.
Love you too, Bani ma'am!
Nishi!
Nishi, slow down!
Wait, you'll hurt yourself.
Bani ma'am, tell me,
how did you see me again?
Ma'am, hurry up. We will get late.
Come, ma'am, come. Hurry up.
Up.
And down.
Nisha,
up to your tricks again?
Sorry, ma'am. I have eaten the candy.
Sorry.
Left. Right.
Left. Right. Left…
Nisha?
Nisha? What's wrong?
Bani ma'am,
I think she has got food poisoning.
I'll take her to Joypurra General Hospital
to get some medicines.
You know, she's not going
to be eating any more junk food.
-Come on, let's go, Nishi.
-What… What did she eat?
How many times have I told you
not to eat junk food?
You please don't worry, Bani.
Nisha will be fine very soon.
"When love is in the air,
the heart bubbles."
Hello, Uma.
Last time, the filter
was not changed properly.
That's why I thought I would come
and fix your purifier again.
Even though, you didn't raise a complaint.
Some water?
Exactly what I have to fix.
This isn't out of my love for the job,
but love for my neighbor.
Is it done?
Bani,
your back must be hurting
from filling buckets of water, right?
I need to leave for work.
It's getting late.
All right, I'll see you soon.
Even I'll be back soon.
Listen, Gokul. You're headed towards
the checkpoint, aren't you?
Could you give me a ride, please?
A month ago, three girls were abducted.
Seems like the entire city's
-under a curse.
-ID?
-What?
-Go.
But after coming here,
the new senior officer has a done a lot
to tighten the security
in and around the city, isn't it?
Right.
Open the trunk and check it properly.
-Wait, where are you going?
-What's your name? Let him go.
Open the trunk. Hurry up and open it.
-Let them go.
-You can go.
Jhunu Amba, until I get my daughter back,
I will not leave Joypurra.
For that,
you'll have to first hide your fears.
You will have to become
a part of this city.
There is no one as fierce as a mother
when it comes to protecting her child.
Remember.
As a child,
everyone would applaud your acrobatics
because you preferred
to do it blindfolded.
My Liliya's not done yet!
You have the power to see with your ears.
No one believes that
a blind woman can be dangerous.
Your vision is getting better now.
But to truly see Joypurra,
you will have to remain blind.
Ma, you couldn't find me.
Your ma will always find you,
my little swallow.
Always.
Remember,
Gokul shouldn't know any of this.
If this demon called Blackhole
ever sets eyes on him,
that will be the end of him.
In the epic Mahabharat,
Gandhari blindfolded herself
for her husband.
You will blindfold yourself
to vanquish that demon
for your daughter Mishty.
Something big is going to happen
in the old warehouse of Dakkhinpara.
Police security
has been removed from there.
It's possible that the girls
have been kept there.
We don't have much time.
-The delivery was made a while ago.
-That's good.
-Was everything accounted for?
-Oh, absolutely.
Let's see.
It's already being loaded
onto another truck.
You don't worry about that.
I'll manage it.
-I'll go and check. Hmm.
-Okay.
Yeah, it's going to be a long…
Don't worry.
I've already sent them the location.
Yes, sir?
We are just about to leave for Para Nagar.
Everything's ready here.
Hello?
There's no issue.
Got you! Ma couldn't find me.
My little swallow.
The girls may have been here
for a short while.
Liliya, come on let's go. Come on.
Sir, we were stationed
at the Devitalaganj Police Station.
But we were tipped off
that an abducted girl
was being taken away in a white van.
Which has headed towards Joypurra.
We are on our way back
to follow that lead.
Yeah. Dutta, come in. Dutta!
Sir, turn left from Chaumukhi Square.
Sir.
All right. Dutta.
Uh, we're taking the shortcut.
You just stay on the tail.
Huh? Stay on it. Stay on it.
Sir. Dutta sir.
Where is the girl?
Sir…
The kidnapped girl was transported
in this very van.
Weren't you also tracking
the same van with us
which was on its way from Devitalaganj?
The number plate is the same as the van
that crossed the Joypurra border
40 minutes earlier.
But, uh, when we searched inside,
there were only vegetables in it.
Only vegetables.
There was an abduction report
filed two days ago.
Where was it filed from?
The one two days ago was from Dhoopanagar.
So what's the distance between Joypurra--
Uh, must be around 50 to 55 kilometers.
Uh, go and check what's happening there.
Not one girl has been kidnapped
from Joypurra in the last month.
But instead, they're being kidnapped
from the neighboring areas.
Uttamanagar.
Dhoopanagar.
Pakhandpur.
Devitalaganj.
Padmabari.
However, all the abducted girls
were last seen in either Joypurra
or the bordering areas of Joypurra.
We have the answer to our question.
This gang is mostly active
only in Joypurra.
That means all the abducted girls
are going to be smuggled out of Joypurra.
Sanjukta, uh…
All the roads which are leading
out of Joypurra are sealed, right?
Yes, sir. They're all sealed.
But there are a few trading routes
which opened during the festival
of the goddess.
For the import and export of incense,
lamps, idols and other things.
They will open,
but under heavy surveillance.
Right.
So, it is possible
that they'll use the festival as a cover
to get the girls out of Joypurra.
Sir, should we just
have the festival cancelled this year?
We can't do that.
The Bahurupi community have been granted
special rights by the government.
We can't stop them.
Um…
Call him. What… What's his name?
Sir, Mr. Dutta. Just a minute.
Mr. Dutta!
Yes, madam?
Please come here for a minute.
-Madam?
-Sir.
For the festival next week,
what do you think are the trading routes?
Sir, Kalpataru Nagar,
Chaumukhi Chowk,
and, uh, the Joypurra docks.
These are the important routes.
And who is on police duty in these areas?
Why, uh…
Officer Saha.
Though the final duty chart
will be out only next week.
Just before the festival.
The good news is that the swelling
on your optic nerve has completely gone.
But, uh,
is there any improvement in vision?
No.
Uh, all right.
I'll write a new prescription. Come.
I'm changing the medicine.
And in a month's time,
we'll run another test.
And here are your reports.
Thank you, doctor.
Sorry.
Nisha, you've become so mischievous.
Should we give you two injections?
One in the morning and one at night.
-It will take your pain away.
-No.
-Yes, yes, yes.
-No, no, no.
My good girl.
If I get the poke, even you'll get one.
Oh, really?
But I'm a good girl.
But, Mummy, even you're naughty at times.
-Do you want some more?
-No, no. No.
-You're done?
-I am done.
Okay. Now lie down.
The other day, you could barely move.
"My tummy's hurting. My tummy's hurting."
My tummy was hurting.
Your tummy was hurting, not mine.
Not mine, your tummy.
-Nisha, how are you feeling today?
-Mummy.
I am good.
Much better. Come on, let's see.
Take a deep breath.
Hey, get me a cup of tea.
Yes, sir!
One cup of tea, please.
Saha.
During the festival,
the export of idols, lamps,
handicrafts, everything will be halted.
This is the season for local businesses
to earn extra money.
Actually the Bahurupi people
are natives of the city.
We all have come here from other places.
Since ancient times,
there's been a practice here.
The practice of sacrificing the girls
to please the Goddess.
This is land of the Bahurupis.
Don't mess with them.
All roads leading out of Joypurra
will remain shut.
Revoke the clearance.
Now.
Dada Bhai, the new officer has shut down
the trade routes with immediate effect.
So will the consignment
have to be taken out
from another city now?
The consignments will definitely leave
only from the city of Joypurra.
Because Joypurra
is astrologically suited.
When the stars align favourably…
and the netherworlds calls,
at that time,
the girls will leave Joypurra.
They'll disappear even as the officers
will be keeping a watch on us.
Using Plan Zero.
-Papa! Papa! Papa!
-Mishty!
Papa! Papa!
-Papa!
Mishty! Mishty!
Topical medication
won't work internally.
Special herbs are required
for a complete cure.
There are two sides to Joypurra.
One that you can see with the naked eye.
And the other…
a dark one beneath
that's hidden away.
Lift your foot for a moment.
These tunnels have a long history.
The rebellion against the British Raj,
the greed of drug cartels.
And now…
The visible Joypurra can be handled
by the police by barricading it.
But the Joypurra beneath…
…the invisible one,
how does one deal with that?
But the JSF has shut the tunnels
and sealed all of them.
The government register
does not have all the records.
And who knows,
maybe a tunnel somewhere
has been left open.
Where can I find these open tunnels?
Looks like an old map of the city.
This old map will lead you
to those tunnels.
But…
you'll have to locate them yourself.
Hello?
Can I get a relaxing head massage
with hot oil, please?
Yes, sure, sir.
-I'll go heat up the oil and come.
-Yeah, sure.
The word is out that something big
is going to happen in Joypurra
through these dark and dangerous tunnels.
And if Goddess Chaumukhi wishes,
she'll help you,
and you'll find your daughter.
Saha mentioned
something about the Bahurupis.
This tribe walks around freely
in disguise.
They watch and observe everything.
But they go unnoticed.
We should blend in with them
to get some leads.
Sanjukta, be on it.
Reports of dead bodies
are not being filed at the police station.
Sir, please, we need your help.
Oh, hell! You're back again?
We can't find your child's body.
I'd rather be looking
for a child who's alive
than be looking
your child's body, isn't it?
I can't understand
where these girls have just disappeared.
And at the same time,
the girls are being taken to a place
called Lal Bari.
Spicy puffed rice!
Can't tell
whether they are dead or alive.
And strangely,
everyone in this area is curious
to know what goes on there.
Only you can go inside
and find out, Liliya.
Spicy puffed rice!
Yes?
Uh, is Sarita at home?
Who?
You've got the wrong house.
Can you… Oh, God.
Lane number three.
Uh, that way?
Yes.
Okay.
Sorry, sorry.
I'm… I'm looking
for lane number three.
Can you…
Tiny little swallow Cute little swallow
Lost in the woods, this little swallow
Tiny little swallow
Cute little swallow
Lost in this woods
This little swallow
Are you sure?
Yes, we have spoken to them,
but how did it happen so suddenly?
Hmm, Bani.
The hospital just called to say
that Nisha's condition
had suddenly deteriorated.
We've lost her.
Uh, Nisha Mitra.
Sorry, ma'am. Her parents are doing
the paperwork to take the body.
I can't let you go in.
It's not allowed.
Listen, please. Uh, I'm her teacher.
I just need two minutes.
I need to sprinkle some holy water on her.
That's all.
I'll leave immediately after that.
Uh, I'll take her inside.
Bani ma'am,
come with me. I'll show you the way.
Okay, thank you. Yeah.
I was just telling her
that I'll be back soon.
I… I'll be back in two minutes.
It won't take very long.
Be careful. To the left. This way.
Nisha Mitra's body.
Come here.
Wait. Right here. Here.
-Bani ma'am.
-Hmm?
-Nisha.
-Huh.
Bani ma'am…
Please don't touch the body.
Sprinkle it on the side here.
I can't breathe.
-May I have some water?
-Yeah, yeah, sure.
Relax, Bani ma'am. Sit down. Sit here.
You're just stressed out.
Please sit here.
I'll get you some tea and cookies. Okay?
Hello, Jhunu Amba?
Nisha's condition didn't deteriorate.
She's been kidnapped.
They've declared her dead
by passing somebody else's body as hers.
Explains why children's bodies
are being picked up
from Para Nagar, Madhupalli,
and areas around Bhadrapur.
And the police here are not
registering complaints about the bodies.
I'm quite sure that Nisha's right here.
In Joypurra Hospital.
Something's going on here.
We might get to know
something about Mishty.
Please come back, Jhunu Amba.
Everything is completed.
The van has arrived.
-Take her down carefully.
-Yeah, yeah.
Sukhit Sarkar, step aside.
Please come inside.
Uh, um…
Where's the pharmacy here?
Is anyone around?
-Anyone around?
-Yes.
-Where's the pharmacy here?
-That way.
That way?
That way, there.
Attention, all staff!
This is code 256.
-The hospital sewer pipeline has burst.
-Please wait for some time.
Caution is advised
to everyone in the hospital.
This is code 256.
Oh, my God. He's injured.
-You go there and check.
-You both go there and search.
Who's over there? Even he's injured!
Where?
-Can someone help me?
-Boss will get angry.
How did he get in here?
Four bags of clothes
and three with children.
Yeah, yeah, understood. You know code 256?
Hurry up.
We need to make the delivery on time.
Pick it up quickly.
Everything's a mess.
Hurry up and leave now.
Hey.
Where is the other bag gone?
Oh, hello. Go now.
It was right here.
Hurry up and leave now, come on.
Come on, hurry up.
The hospital has complained.
That the girl we abducted from the school,
Nisha, wasn't measured correctly.
She is six inches shorter than the corpse
we swapped her with.
If the parents figure it out,
Plan Zero is finished.
-It's not my fault.
-Keep it low.
The body was marked at Laal Badi.
You should ask Mukesh.
Four feet.
He said four feet, accordingly,
we found a girl in that school,
and gave her candy.
Bani ma'am,
I think she has got food poisoning.
It's possible that the hospital
didn't do a proper job. Perhaps the name--
According to our boss,
everything was done correctly.
We have injected the body
of the four-feet girl with the chemical.
Once it's fully absorbed,
no one will recognize her.
Now, go.
Drive around the block and be back.
She'll be ready by then.
I mean the boss really has a devious mind.
With this new officer watching us,
we won't be to take a single girl
out of Joypurra.
Who said the girls were leaving?
Come on, leave.
Gobind, hurry up.
Uma ma'am wants everything done
as soon as possible.
Hmm, all right.
Sir, the festival
of the Goddess has begun today.
And security has been increased
considerably.
Main Chowk, Toll Naka,
Joypurra Docks, and also on the beach.
You need to be extremely alert.
And also, talk to your sources
on the ground.
Yes, sir.
Somu, come in.
Churni ma'am. Churni ma'am.
Churni ma'am.
-Bani?
-Ma'am, I…
What are you doing here?
-Are you all right?
-Churni ma'am!
Arrangements for tonight's immersion
are going very well.
And, yes, I have kept
your laundry bag inside.
Good morning, Bani ma'am.
Are you okay?
Take care.
Love you, too.
What's the matter? Tell me.
I'll come later.
-Huh?
-Ma'am, I'll come later.
Is everything okay, Bani?
I thought I was looking
for the demon of Joypurra.
But what I didn't know
is that Joypurra had demons everywhere.
In fact, Joypurra itself is the demon.
This old map will lead you
to those tunnels.
And who knows,
maybe a tunnel somewhere
has been left open.
Come on, run.
Bani.
Where did you go earlier?
What's the matter with you today?
I wasn't feeling too well,
so I came back to meet the girls.
That's nice.
Hmm. Come here. Sit down.
I'll get you a cup of tea.
Tiny little swallow
Cute little swallow
Lost in the woods
This little swallow
Flying, flying far away
She lost her way
And went astray
On a branch, all alone
No friend to call her own
Then another came laughing by
Mishty! Mi…
I really love this poem.
It's my favourite.
Who taught you this?
A friend.
So, tell me.
Did any new friends come here today?
Huh?
No, aunty. No new friends came today.
But a few days ago,
when we went to the beach,
Dakkhinpara Beach,
my friend Pinky
didn't come back with us from there.
The water demon and the fish-eating ghost,
they scared her and took her into the sea.
Churni ma'am also told us that
we should not play with our new friends.
She said they need to rest.
Hey, you're not allowed to go in there!
Wanna play hide and seek?
-Huh?
-Yes.
You count to 20, all right?
And I'll go hide somewhere. Come on.
This way. Start.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Hello, Mr. Gokul?
I'm calling from the school.
Has Bani reached home?
Bani… Not yet. Why?
She went to see Nisha at the hospital.
She hasn't come back to school,
and she's not answering her phone.
Uh, where could she go?
Bani!
Tea!
Eighteen.
Nineteen.
Got you!
-Let's go. Come on.
-Bani.
Churni ma'am.
We were playing hide and seek.
I'm feeling a lot better now.
Maybe, I should go home now.
Tea?
Well, I'll come… I'll come by tomorrow.
I'll leave now.
All right.
I did find the laundry bags,
but the girls weren't in them.
You sure you saw them being taken inside?
I saw Somesh taking them inside.
There has to be a secret way.
Go. She's standing at the gate.
I'll go and check in on Uma.
-Call me.
-Yes.
You asked me to come
to Shishukal immediately.
Is there any information?
We'll talk later.
Bahurupi?
Mm-hmm.
Nice. Would you like to perform
for the children?
Uh, ugh…
-Shall we?
-Hmm.
We need to get the girls out today.
After that, you disappear for a few days.
All right.
-The boss will let you know.
-Okay.
-When and where to meet.
-Do you have masks?
Tiger, bear, or monkey?
-Monkey.
Want to try it on?
Looks really nice.
Okay.
Oh, Bani!
-Oh.
-Hey, Uma.
Yes.
-Oh, Bani.
-Yes?
I'll see you in the evening,
we'll have tea together.
-Yeah.
-All right?
Yeah.
Bani ma'am, how are you?
Saurabh!
Is everything all right?
-Yes, it is.
-Hmm.
Go and check there.
Amba, listen.
I'm at the Biswas Wire Factory.
Please come here soon.
Liliya, Liliya, let's go.
Bani, you're really blind.
Churni already told me you can see.
So I made some inquiries.
And I got to know a lot about you.
Things that even you don't know
about yourself.
And your dear Jhunu Amba.
A mother to you.
In reality, a witch.
Years ago, your dearest Jhunu
trusted her brother
and sent you all with him
to perform acrobatics on the streets.
And her dear brother later sold
you four girls to us for some money.
And, Bani, you were one of them.
Let me go!
-Run! Run!
-Get up. Get up.
Get down. Keep quiet, you.
-Come!
-Run!
Come, lady. Quick… Quickly.
Run!
Come on!
No! No!
Leave us.
Hey, what the heck!
He's driving our van! Come on!
Come on, come on! Quick!
That's where you met your husband Gokul.
You were lucky he saved you.
But we have a rule.
A girl for a girl.
Jhunu Amba's granddaughter,
Dulari, paid the price
for those four girls
and was picked up in the bargain.
But this
Jhunu Amba wouldn't give up.
In exchange for her granddaughter,
this woman traded your daughter.
Last year, in Chaksuliyapada,
your dearest Jhunu Amba made a deal
and gave us your address.
How would we know where you,
your husband and your daughter were?
We picked her up.
Yeah.
Hey!
Did you give the address?
Did you tell them?
I only gave Gokul's address.
I made a deal for Gokul
in exchange for Dulari.
I didn't know
they would take Mishty instead.
When Mishty was taken,
all I did was look for her day and night.
I was helpless.
Please understand, Liliya.
-I'm a mother too.
-Hey!
Don't you call yourself a mother.
You're nothing but a wretched woman.
Life is chain of events.
The past, the present, and the future,
it's all connected.
My Liliya is not done yet.
Bani!
What happened?
-Are you okay?
-Let's go from here.
Let's leave.
Straight and right.
I am the one who can't see.
Clearly didn't realize you could.
A father can die
a million deaths for his child.
And I couldn't even protect my daughter.
I couldn't save her.
You must have thought,
what's the point of telling me all this?
Gokul, I didn't tell you because it'd mean
putting your life at risk.
-They would have come and hurt--
-What did you think?
That I just sit at the toll booth
just to issue tickets all day?
Huh?
Day and night, I was only thinking of ways
to get Mishty back.
I was trying to find out
everything about the Blackhole.
We are the ones disguising ourselves
just like the Bahurupi folk.
I thought I'll… I'll disguise myself
as a blind woman
to find out about the Blackhole gang.
And I managed to do so as well.
Uma, Churni, Gobind,
they're all in this together.
And Somesh, I saw him a few hours ago.
He changed the girls' names,
disguised them
and took them to Shishukal,
the children's home.
I just don't understand
how they're taking the girls
out of the city from inside the orphanage.
Through these tunnels.
Something big will happen tonight
during Goddess Chaumukhi's veneration.
I have to inform the senior officer.
And please don't go anywhere
until I'm back, okay?
I'll leave now.
Gokul, I'll be waiting for you.
Come back soon.
I'll be back very soon.
Everyone stay alert in areas
near the port.
No consignment without my permission
will leave the port, okay?
-Sure.
-In case of emergency…
-Kabir sir!
-Stop.
I need to tell you
something important, sir. Please.
Sir, as per my research,
there could also be tunnels in the area
between Shishukal and Dakkhinpara.
Why weren't these tunnels mentioned
in the list of underground tunnels?
Sir, this report
only mentions the sealed tunnels
that lead out of the city.
Or the ones that have been marked
in the threat report.
Hello, officer.
I have a search warrant for the premises.
Jaishree, bring the keys.
You go move all the kids to one side.
Come on, children.
Pradeep, open the doors.
Search all the rooms.
I want every corner of this place
to be checked thoroughly.
Sir.
According to the register,
there should be 30 girls.
And all 30 girls are here.
Also, there aren't any hidden doors
or even a secret tunnel.
I'm on my way.
-Pradeep.
-Yes, sir.
Call the unit.
-Let's go.
-We're leaving.
Now!
Yes, Bani?
Gokul.
Gokul? Hel--
Through these tunnels,
something big will happen tonight
during Goddess Chaumukhi's veneration.
Hey, you're not allowed to go in there!
All the main smuggling routes
had been shut down
during JSF's anti-tunnels operation.
Churni ma'am,
arrangements for tonight's immersion
are going very well.
-Arise, O Mother Chaumukhi!
-Arise!
Yeah, I've been looking after things--
-Sir, the senior officer's on the line.
-You go.
Sir?
Leave right away with rest.
-Okay.
-I'll deal with the AHTU.
Copy.
Where were you taking the girl?
Who are you? Tell me who are you?
-Whose girl is it, huh? Tell me!
-Papa!
-That's my daughter.
Awaken, Chaumukhi. Awaken!
The local police were supposed
to be on duty. Where are they?
Sir, we were patrolling
the Dakkhinpara port.
And then,
suddenly we were called here, sir.
By whom?
But a few days ago,
when we went to the beach,
Dakkhinpara Beach,
Pinky didn't come back with us from there.
Through these tunnels,
something big will happen tonight
during Goddess Chaumukhi's veneration.
There are still some secret routes
in Joypurra.
Pinky didn't come back with us from there.
The water demon and the fish-eating ghost,
they scared her and took her into the sea.
It's believed that centuries ago,
there lived a demon here
by the name of Magrasur.
He kidnapped children
and took them to the netherworld.
To save them, Chaumukhi
the goddess of this land herself
descended into the netherworld.
Officer Kabir.
It's a request.
Please go back.
You made up all those fake stories.
Because you wanted the Bahurupis
to take the fall for the Blackhole gang.
Huh?
Love you, too.
Hurry up. Only two more kids to take.
Hold her properly. Go.
Go, go, go. Fast! Run!
We found Nisha, Gokul.
The other girls are here as well.
Our Mishty must also be here.
Let's find her.
Let's call the police.
They will come and take the girls.
They are safe now.
Wha… What?
Huh?
Bani, the girls will go
where they're supposed to go.
Why?
Gokul?
Before I met you,
I used to work for the Blackhole.
Girls were being supplied
to the other cities,
and I used to make fake IDs for them
from my shop.
Once I had to go to the field
to deliver a fake ID.
And that's when I realized
what I was a part of.
When I saw you there…
my entire world changed.
After rescuing you from there,
I felt as if I have redeemed myself.
I thought I had Blackhole behind forever,
but Blackhole never left me.
Dulari, Jhunu Amba, and our Mishty,
that monster had devoured all of them.
I had no clue that they were operating
from Joypurra.
Nor did I know
how they were taking the girls from there.
-Yes, Bani?
-Hey.
Dada Bhai wants to see you.
They picked me up
from the children's shelter.
Hello.
You know it very well
that Blackhole will never leave you.
It's a shadow, and there's only one thing
that can release you.
Death.
And you know our rules.
A girl in exchange for a girl.
You want to save your daughter Mishty?
Then help us in sending the others girls
out of the city.
The wheel of time is turning,
turning, turning, turning and turning.
The other day,
you failed to protect your Mishty.
But this time, don't fail.
It's all up to you.
If I have to save our Mishty,
I'll have to work with them again, Bani.
It's either these girls,
or our Mishty.
I won't let anything happen to Mishty.
I'm her father, Bani.
How can I sacrifice my own daughter?
And how can I sacrifice so many daughters?
I'm a mother.
Please think about our Mishty, Bani.
Think about our daughter.
Daughter?
A man who sells daughters
doesn't deserved to be called a father.
So dare you call Mishty your daughter.
You didn't even give it a thought
You didn't even ask me once
You didn't even take a good look at me
You left me all alone
And walked away
-O, my love
-I can't live without you
I can't die without you
-O my love
-Once broken, it can't be put together
I flourished because of you
My heart shattered for you
-O my love
-Once broken, it can't be put together
You didn't even give it a thought
Mishty…
-Gokul. Gokul. Gokul!
-Mishty…
-Gokul?
I never once thought
that you would find your way here.
Huh?
Gokul, in exchange for his Mishty,
was ready to sacrifice
so many other girls.
Because he was in a moral dilemma.
He had to choose his daughter.
Helpless as a father,
what could he have done?
But…
little did he know
that just like the other girls,
even Mishty would be sent
far away across the sea.
And there's something else he didn't know.
That even after doing all this,
he wouldn't get his daughter back.
According to our plan
and the alignment of stars,
everything was falling into place.
Under the guise of the Bahurupi people,
the sea, the dark tunnels
and in Chaumukhi's city, Joypurra,
I would have taken the girls
and like Demon Magrasur disappeared.
But then, you…
But then, you came to Joypurra.
The other day, I let you go
thinking you were just a helpless mother.
Tiny little swallow
Cute little swallow
Lost in the woods
This little swallow
She lost her way and went astray
Went astray
Woosh…
The girls will definitely be gone.
And along with them,
you too.
Look at your daughter one last time.
Because this time, too,
you won't be able to save her.
And neither will your goddess be able
to save all those little girls.
Bani, say a final good bye
to your little swallow Mishty.
Tiny little swallow, lost in the woods
Tiny little swallow…
Uh, lost in the woods.
Tiny little swallow.
Leave from the Dakkhinpara gate,
meet me at entry behind the port.
Mamma.
Not this time.
My daughter, O my darling
You're a blessing from the Lord
My darling
For a smile of yours
I can sacrifice the whole world
I wonder why
You didn't tell me fairytales
Why did you teach me to fly
When this world was going to
Cage me and clip my wings
Tell me, O mother
Why did you give birth to me?
My daughter, O my darling
Forgive me, my darling
You're a little glass doll
In a stonehearted world
Sometimes with authority
Sometimes with deceit
Sometimes it tears us apart
Sometimes it steals us away
Sometimes with authority
Sometimes with deceit
Sometimes it tears us apart
Sometimes it steals us away
They don't even spare Goddesses
This world is full of monsters
My daughter, O my darling
It's a mother's promise to you
I'll make sure
That this world
Will be fit for you now on
My daughter, O my darling
You're the reason for my joy
For a teardrop from your eyes
I can sacrifice myself
To end this world
My daughter, O my darling
You're the reason for my joy
For a teardrop from your eyes
I can sacrifice myself
To end this world
You didn't tell me fairytales
Why did you teach me to fly
When this world was going to
Cage me and clip my wings
Tell me, O mother
Why did you give birth to me?
My daughter, O my darling
Forgive me, my darling
You're a little glass doll
In a stonehearted world
You didn't even give it a thought
You didn't even ask me once
You didn't even take a good look at me
So much happened while you were gone
How much I suffered for you
You didn't even bother
To look back once
You left me all alone and walked away
-O, my love
-I can't live without you
I can't die without you
-O my love
-Once broken, it can't be put together
I flourished because of you
My heart shattered for you
-O my love
-Once broken, it can't be put together
How can I forget you?
You're part of my being
You laugh within me
Like the blood in my veins
In every breath of mine
It's only you
-O, my love
-I can't live without you
I can't die without you
-O my love
-Once broken, it can't be put together
This cruel heart doesn't listen to me
Even though you broke it
It prays for you, o my love
It may hate you
But it doesn't forget you
Even when it's away from you
It holds on to you
O, my love
Even when apart, may we be one
May we find each other
Both of us have but one wish
But one wish
-O, my love
-I can't live without you
I can't die without you
-O my love
-Once broken, it can't be put together
I flourished because of you
My heart shattered for you
-O, my love
-I can't live without you
I can't die without you
-O my love
-Once broken, it can't be put together
-O, my love
-I can't live without you
I can't die without you
-O my love
-Once broken, it can't be put together
I flourished because of you
My heart shattered for you
-O my love
-Once broken, it can't be put together
You didn't even give it a thought
You didn't even ask me once
You didn't even take a good look at me